http://www.fantasycars.com/about/#privacypolicy

About | Contact | Disclaimer | Privacy Policy | FantasyCars
Toggle navigation
CARS
Alfa Romeo (2)
Aston Martin (7)
Audi (2)
BMW (4)
Bugatti (1)
Chevrolet (2)
Ferrari (15)
Ford (2)
Jaguar (1)
Koenigsegg (2)
Lamborghini (5)
Lotus (4)
Maserati (2)
McLaren (3)
Mercedes (2)
Nissan (1)
Pagani (2)
Porsche (6)
About FantasyCars
FantasyCarsTM started as one of the Internet's very first car websites, launching in 1998 and becoming one of the 10 most visited car websites by 2003.
Today, FantasyCars aims to become the premier automotive digital media brand, the de-facto source for reviews, photos, videos and technical data for the world's most desirable cars, that we like to call FantasyCarsTM.
We are currently building an extensive network of contributors worldwide. If your passion is cars, get in touch.
Contact FantasyCars
You can contact FantasyCars via:
- Email at info@fantasycars.com
Disclaimer
The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by FantasyCars and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.
In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.
Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of FantasyCars. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.
Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, FantasyCars takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.
Privacy Policy
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@fantasycars.com.
At FantasyCars, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by FantasyCars and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, FantasyCars makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
FantasyCars does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on FantasyCars send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
FantasyCars has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. FantasyCars's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
About
Contact
Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
facebook
twitter
google+
© 2020 FantasyCars . All Rights Reserved.
